For Sarah, we're going to do square with a rounded edge.
That way she's got the durability of square in her everyday life of the things that she picks up, especially being that she's a trainer and has to pick up weights.
The rounded edge we're going to give her on the corners is just so she doesn't scratch herself, scratch any of her clients, or tear any of her clothes or pantyhose.
You could also do a round nail.
You could do a straight square nail, where you have pointy ends.
Or you could have an oval nail, which is tapered at the top.
Hold on to your nail file so that it doesn't come flying out your hand like it just did.
What I'm doing is just making sure that there isn't any acrylic or glue stuck on to her skin.
I'm filing the sides first to make sure that they come out straight.
Then I'm filing the tip.
This is how you file the nails after you've applied the acrylic.
After you've done the first five, you're just going to do the same to the other hand.
And then just hold them out and make sure that they match up evenly.